<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1" standalone="no"?>
<xml xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance">
	<SequenceKey>4</SequenceKey>
	<Item id="-38">
		<SubId>6</SubId>
		<VN>Extra Towels</VN>
		<EN>Extra Towels</EN>
		<image>1329721148180.jpg</image>
		<Des>Safeguard your room keys at all times. Should you misplace your
			room key, notify a member of Guest Services. Proper identification is
			required to receive a new key.</Des>
	</Item>
	<Item id="-39">
		<SubId>6</SubId>
		<VN>Admittance</VN>
		<EN>Admittance</EN>
		<image>Housekeeping/mainternance1.png</image>
		<Des>Do not admit unknown persons in your room without properly
			identifying them. Any concerns regarding a person¿s identify should
			be conveyed to our Security Team.</Des>
	</Item>
	<Item id="-40">
		<SubId>6</SubId>
		<VN>Overview</VN>
		<EN>Overview</EN>
		<image>Housekeeping/mainternance2.png</image>
		<Des>The Hotel Security department is staffed with training officers
			24 hours a day and is available to assist guests at any time. We
			value your safety and the security of your personal property. We urge
			you to take advantage of the following recommendations.</Des>
	</Item>
	<Item id="-41">
		<SubId>6</SubId>
		<VN>Room Locks</VN>
		<EN>Room Locks</EN>
		<image>Housekeeping/mainternance3.png</image>
		<Des>For additional security while in your guest room please utilize
			the dead bolt as well as all door locking features. This will prevent
			the door from being opened from the outside. A Do Not Disturb hanger
			is also available for your added privacy.</Des>
	</Item>
	<Item id="-42">
		<SubId>6</SubId>
		<VN>In-Room Safe</VN>
		<EN>In-Room Safe</EN>
		<image>Dining/griddle_1.png</image>
		<Des>For your convenience, a complimentary safe is located in every
			guest room.</Des>
	</Item>
	<Item id="-43">
		<SubId>6</SubId>
		<VN>Safe Deposit Boxes</VN>
		<EN>Safe Deposit Boxes</EN>
		<image>Dining/griddle2.png</image>
		<Des>Additional safe deposit boxes are available by the Front Desk at
			no additional cost.</Des>
	</Item>
	<Item id="-44">
		<SubId>6</SubId>
		<VN>Telephone Calls</VN>
		<EN>Telephone Calls</EN>
		<image>Dining/griddle3.png</image>
		<Des>Promptly report any suspicious or indecent telephone calls to our
			Security Team.</Des>
	</Item>
	<Item id="-45">
		<SubId>6</SubId>
		<VN>Emergency Assistance</VN>
		<EN>Emergency Assistance</EN>
		<image>Dining/griddle4.png</image>
		<Des>In the event of a "Life Threatening Emergency" please call 113
			from any phone inside the hotel. Immediately after calling 113 please
			report the emergency to the Security Team by calling Ext. 55. A
			security officer will respond immediately to assist you.</Des>
	</Item>
	<Item id="-46">
		<SubId>6</SubId>
		<VN>Non-Emergency Assistence</VN>
		<EN>Non-Emergency Assistence</EN>
		<image>1325817936211.gif</image>
		<Des>For non-emergency assistance from the Security Department (to
			report minor injuries, losses, noise complaints and other
			disturbances) please call Ext. 55. Please give your full name and
			room number when calling. A security officer will respond to assist
			you as soon as possible.</Des>
	</Item>
	<Item id="-47">
		<SubId>6</SubId>
		<VN>Fire Alarm</VN>
		<EN>Fire Alarm</EN>
		<image>Exchange/CAD.png</image>
		<Des>When there is a file alarm, the strobe lights in your guest room
			will flash and a public announcement regarding the alarm
			investigation will be made. Please listen carefully to all public
			announcements for further instruction.</Des>
	</Item>
	<Item id="-48">
		<SubId>6</SubId>
		<VN>Fire Evacuation</VN>
		<EN>Fire Evacuation</EN>
		<image>Exchange/EUR.png</image>
		<Des>Do not use elevators. There are guest stairwells for the guest
			floors. When an evacuation is necessary and evacuation announcement
			will sound over the PA system. Go to the nearest stairwell and walk
			calmly down the stairs, exit the building and stand by to receive
			further instructions. Please also refer to the evacuation map placed
			on the back of each guest room entry door.</Des>
	</Item>
	<Item id="-49">
		<SubId>6</SubId>
		<VN>Severe Weather Emergency</VN>
		<EN>Severe Weather Emergency</EN>
		<image />
		<Des>In the event of severe weather emergency, an annoucement will be
			made over th PA system.</Des>
	</Item>
	<Item id="17">
		<SubId>4</SubId>
		<VN>Overview</VN>
		<EN>Overview</EN>
		<image>Hotel/1305521380627.png</image>
		<Des>&amp;lt;h3&amp;gt;Business
			Services&amp;lt;/h3&amp;gt;&amp;#160;-&amp;#160;Business Services:
			Copy service; Fax service; Full-service business center;
			network/internet printing; Notary public; overnight delivery/pickup;
			post/parcel&amp;lt;br&amp;gt;-&amp;#160;Business Center: a business
			center is located next to the front desk. The business center
			features 2 Mac computers and a printer. Open 24 hours.</Des>
	</Item>
	<Item id="990">
		<SubId>1</SubId>
		<VN>123</VN>
		<EN>123</EN>
		<image>noimage.gif</image>
		<Des>&amp;lt;br&amp;gt;</Des>
	</Item>
	<Item id="9">
		<SubId>2</SubId>
		<VN>Ti&amp;#7879;n nghi trong ph&amp;#242;ng</VN>
		<EN>Ti&amp;#7879;n nghi trong ph&amp;#242;ng</EN>
		<image>ExtraTowels.png</image>
		<Des>EVOLVE&amp;lt;br&amp;gt;As you enter the room, insert your key
			card in the small white box near the light switch to activate the
			system. This will turn on your in-room lighting, LCD control panel in
			the bathroom and heating/air conditioning. When exiting your room,
			please remove your key card. This will disengage the room lights and
			TV as well as reset your heating/air conditioning unit to a preset
			confort level and set the foyer light on a 10 second delay shut
			off.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;</Des>
	</Item>
	<Item id="10">
		<SubId>2</SubId>
		<VN>Media Hub</VN>
		<EN>Media Hub</EN>
		<image>Hotel/room/1305521380619.png</image>
		<Des>The Media Hub has been installed for your convenience. Play your
			own TV programs, game, movies and music through the in-room TV or
			sound system. Just select the channel listed below next to the
			function that you would like to use, plug in your device an go
			&amp;lt;br /&amp;gt;
			1. Composite Audio/Video: Plug in iPod, MP3 Player, DVD player, game
			console, or digital camera. &amp;lt;br /&amp;gt;
			2. S-Video: Super Video enabled video cameras and laptops &amp;lt;br
			/&amp;gt;
			3. Mini Stereo Jack: Connect any devaice with a headphone jack, play
			your own music or pod casts. &amp;lt;br /&amp;gt;
			4. VGA (RGB): Laptop computer, browser the internet, play movies, or
			review business presentations &amp;lt;br /&amp;gt;
			5. HDMI: High definition video &amp;lt;br /&amp;gt;
			6. USB (5v) Power: Charge electronic devices &amp;lt;br /&amp;gt;</Des>
	</Item>
	<Item id="12">
		<SubId>2</SubId>
		<VN>Bath Soap</VN>
		<EN>Bath Soap</EN>
		<image>ExtraTowels.png</image>
		<Des>&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;Power
			Outlets&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;There
			are additional outlets in each guest room on the bedside lamp and two
			outlets on the media hub for your convenience. There is also a duplex
			outlet located in the bathroom. Please be advised that when exiting
			the room that the EVOLVE system will terminate power from all
			electrical outlets with the exception of your media
			hub.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;</Des>
	</Item>
	<Item id="13">
		<SubId>2</SubId>
		<VN>Other Room Amenities</VN>
		<EN>Other Room Amenities</EN>
		<image>Hotel/room/1305521380623.png</image>
		<Des>&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;Other Room
			Amenities&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;br&amp;gt;-&amp;#160;
			Ice bucket, glasses, and a refrigerator are located in the
			dresser&amp;lt;br&amp;gt;-&amp;#160;&amp;#160;Hairdryers and
			additional toilet paper are are located in the drawer in the
			bathroom. If your guest room does not have a drawer in the bathroom
			these item will be locate in the
			closet.&amp;lt;br&amp;gt;-&amp;#160;&amp;#160;&amp;#160;Spare
			pillows, blankets, ironing boeard, irons and rebes can be found in
			the
			closet.;&amp;lt;br&amp;gt;-&amp;#160;&amp;#160;&amp;#160;&amp;#160;TV
			&amp;#8211; you can access in room movie and premium as well as local
			programing.</Des>
	</Item>
	<Item id="14">
		<SubId>2</SubId>
		<VN>TV Listing</VN>
		<EN>TV Listing</EN>
		<image>Hotel/room/1305521380624.png</image>
		<Des>1. Welcome Channel &amp;lt;br&amp;gt;
			2. Promo &amp;lt;br&amp;gt;
			3. Hotel &amp;lt;br&amp;gt;
			4. NBC HD &amp;lt;br&amp;gt;
			5. ABC HD &amp;lt;br&amp;gt;
			6. HBO HD &amp;lt;br&amp;gt;
			7. ESPN HD &amp;lt;br&amp;gt;
			8. CNN HD &amp;lt;br&amp;gt;</Des>
	</Item>
</xml>